Hello.
Welcome back.
In this lesson, we are going to see how to set up the S.P.I with DME functionality.
So I've created a new project, as you can see over here, and I've cleared all the pins.
And when I select our S.P.I, I'll come to connectivity S.P.I one like we did earlier.
And then I'm going to set up for foremast.
A duplex mode over here is foremast.
A duplex like this.
Okay, I'm going to set a clock two sixteen so that all of us with a four would use it equally so so
16 over here and everything will be readjusted.
So now we can go back to always pure configuration.
OK.
Come two systems view over here.
When I open this, I should see S.P.I spilling over here.
OK, I've got to open it by clicking here.
Okay, I'll come to parameter certains over here, okay?
We can keep the pre-schooler off, too.
That is fine.
We don't need to reduce it further.
So what makes this project different is we've got to go to DMA settings and at the Yemi.
So I click add and then I'll select S.P.I, our DMA and then.
Oh, add another DMA over here.
40 x.
Click over here, S.P.I, DME, like that.
So now you can go ahead and generally talk code.
I'll come over here, generate code.
I'll give it a name.
S.P.I, dma p I underscore d m a like this.
And then also letter to change the M 32 Kubi d e and then a click generate over here like this.
So this whole project.
So we do like we did earlier.
We start off by creating on our Rixon T x buffer.
I'll just put this here.
We initialize the T X buffer to have some data and we expect to find that data into our X.
If you want, you can take a look at the code generated by a Y.
Cuba makes elections is basically the standard S.P.I code generation to get out with some third generation
for the DMA and setting the DMA interrupt and DMA priority.
You can take a look at that.
And again, if you want to see more about this, you can take a look at the DEHA preference module we
downloaded earlier.
Let's go step by step, um, step by step, um, information on how to deal with each of the whole API.
So over here, I'd just like to interrupt example.
It's exactly the same API, except that the last word is DMA.
So the API is whole, underscore, S.P.I, underscore, transmit and then we have receive.
And then the first argument is the handle of the um, of the S.P.I, which is H.
S P.
I want the second argument is the um it's the T X buffer.
The next argument after this is the R X buffer and then the data side.
We don't need to pass the arm.
We don't need to pass a out.
This one we have to Artemia at the end of the DMA like this.
Okay.
So with DME and interrupt you, we always have to find the, um, the callback function to implement
the callback would require.
It's exactly the same callback we used for the S.P.I interrupt the project um as the receive uh transmit
complete callback.
So we can go and fetch it like we did or come to drive us over here.
Hard drive a source.
And then what we were looking for is S.P.I dot C over here and I can just search the weak keyword.
And it would take me to a control F and then I hit one, two, three, four, five.
So this is our 60 X complete callback and copy.
Put it up here.
And like I said, this Kobuk, you just do something in it, do something first.
You delete the key word and you can just do something, you know, like this.
Earlier on, we were just increment a counter variable, but we can leave it empty so it can go ahead
and build our project or click over here to build.
To build in, then we can go to the debug, click over here or select this.
And then I say, okay, over here.
And I'm going to add my ah ex buffa to the live expressions to see if indeed we received the data when
I put a break point over here.
That's the main function.
Over here, man, I'm just going to click here to put a break point here.
OK.
When I click it to run, it would stop over here.
Sorry.
I want to put a break point at the wall.
One loop.
No, the main function.
Goodness.
Over here.
Like this.
So click here.
And then it stopped over here.
So let's see if our Poffo has the data.
It has to have and indeed it's working.
And this time we transfer Mitton.
Oh, we are.
Yeah.
Transmitting the data.
Using the DMA.
So that's I.
The rest.